(FEET TAPPING)
(TAPE SCRATCHES)
(FUNKY UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ LOST IN A DREAM ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW WHICH WAY TO GO ♪
♪ LET ME SAY ♪
♪ IF YOU ARE ALL THAT YOU SEEM ♪
♪ THEN BABY I'M
MOVIN' WAY TOO SLOW ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN A FOOL BEFORE ♪
♪ WOULDN'T LIKE TO
GET MY LOVE CAUGHT ♪
♪ IN THE SLAMMIN' DOOR ♪
♪ HOW ABOUT SOME
INFORMATION PLEASE ♪
♪ STRAIGHT UP NOW TELL ME ♪
♪ DO YOU REALLY WANNA LOVE
ME FOREVER, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OR AM I CAUGHT
IN A HIT AND RUN ♪
♪ STRAIGHT UP NOW TELL ME ♪
♪ IS IT GONNA BE YOU AND
ME TOGETHER, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OR ARE YOU JUST HAVING FUN ♪
♪ TIME'S STANDING STILL ♪
♪ WAITING FOR SOME ♪
♪ WAITING FOR SOME SMALL CLUE ♪
♪ LET ME TELL YOU NOW ♪
♪ I KEEP GETTING CHILLS ♪
♪ WHEN I THINK YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ WHEN I THINK
YOUR LOVE IS TRUE ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN A FOOL BEFORE ♪
♪ WOULDN'T LIKE TO
GET MY LOVE CAUGHT ♪
♪ IN THE SLAMMIN' DOOR ♪
♪ HOW ABOUT SOME
INFORMATION PLEASE ♪
♪ STRAIGHT UP NOW TELL ME ♪
♪ DO YOU REALLY WANNA LOVE
ME FOREVER, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OR AM I CAUGHT
IN A HIT AND RUN ♪
♪ STRAIGHT UP NOW TELL ME ♪
♪ IS IT GONNA BE YOU AND
ME TOGETHER, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ ARE YOU JUST HAVING FUN ♪
♪ YOU ARE SO HARD TO READ ♪
♪ YOU PLAY HIDE AND SEEK ♪
♪ WITH YOUR TRUE INTENTIONS ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE ONLY PLAYING GAMES ♪
♪ I'LL JUST HAVE TO SAY ♪
♪ BYE, BYE, BYE, BYE,
BYE, BYE, BYE, BYE, BYE ♪
♪ DO, DO YOU LOVE ME ♪
♪ DO, DO YOU LOVE ME, BABY ♪
♪ COME ON NOW ♪
♪ DO, DO YOU LOVE ME ♪
♪ TELL ME BABY ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN A FOOL BEFORE ♪
♪ WOULDN'T LIKE TO
GET MY LOVE CAUGHT ♪
♪ IN THE SLAMMIN' DOOR ♪
♪ ARE YOU MORE THAN HOT FOR ME ♪
♪ OR AM I A PAGE IN
YOUR HISTORY BOOK ♪
♪ I DON'T MEAN TO MAKE DEMANDS ♪
♪ BUT THE WORD AND THE
DEED GO HAND IN HAND ♪
♪ HOW ABOUT SOME
INFORMATION PLEASE ♪
♪ PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE, PLEASE ♪
♪ STRAIGHT UP NOW
TELL ME, TELL ME ♪
♪ STRAIGHT UP NOW TELL ME ♪
♪ DO YOU REALLY WANNA LOVE
ME FOREVER, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OR AM I CAUGHT
IN A HIT AND RUN ♪
♪ STRAIGHT UP NOW TELL ME ♪
♪ IS IT GONNA BE YOU AND
ME TOGETHER, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OR ARE YOU JUST HAVING FUN ♪
♪ STRAIGHT UP NOW TELL ME ♪
♪ DO YOU REALLY WANNA LOVE
ME FOREVER, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OR AM I CAUGHT
IN A HIT AND RUN ♪
♪ STRAIGHT UP NOW TELL ME ♪
♪ IS IT GONNA BE YOU AND
ME TOGETHER, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OR ARE YOU JUST HAVING FUN ♪
♪ STRAIGHT UP NOW TELL ME ♪
♪ DO YOU REALLY WANNA LOVE
ME FOREVER, OH, OH, OH ♪